Office of the Registrar, School of Medicine Records UA075
Tufts Archival Research Center
- Student folders, 1961 -- 2005; UA075.002; 141.6 Linear Feet
  - Cohen, Scott, 1989; UA075.002.049.00016 (Box 49)
  - Cohen, Meyer, 1992; UA075.002.049.00017 (Box 49)
  - Colagiovanni, Steven, 1989; UA075.002.049.00018 (Box 49)
  - Colella, Ryan, 1995; UA075.002.049.00019 (Box 49)
  - Collupy, Heather, 1992; UA075.002.049.00020 (Box 49)
  - Como, Rose, 1990; UA075.002.049.00021 (Box 49)
  - Conlin, Daniel, 1986; UA075.002.049.00022 (Box 49)
  - Conklin, Edward, 1990; UA075.002.049.00023 (Box 49)
  - Coniglio, Cynthia, 1986; UA075.002.049.00024 (Box 49)
  - Connolly, Annamarie, 1991; UA075.002.049.00025 (Box 49)
  - Connolly, Kathleen (formerly Kathleen O'Bien Jachowicz), 1986; UA075.002.049.00026 (Box 49)
  - Connolly, John, 1986; UA075.002.049.00027 (Box 49)
  - Connor Jr., James Francis, 1987; UA075.002.049.00028 (Box 49)
  - Connors, Janine, 1993; UA075.002.049.00029 (Box 49)
  - Constantine, Michael, 1988; UA075.002.049.00030 (Box 49)
  - Cooper, Michael, 1987; UA075.002.049.00031 (Box 49)
  - Coppin, Christophe, 1993; UA075.002.049.00032 (Box 49)
  - Corbett, Helen, 1989; UA075.002.049.00033 (Box 49)
  - Cordy, Roy, 1987; UA075.002.050.00001 (Box 50)
  - Corey, Timothy, 1992; UA075.002.050.00002 (Box 50)
  - Corral, Claudio, 1991; UA075.002.050.00003 (Box 50)
  - Cortell, Eric, 1991; UA075.002.050.00004 (Box 50)
  - Cortez, Stephen, 1989; UA075.002.050.00005 (Box 50)
  - Costanza, Carl, 1992; UA075.002.050.00006 (Box 50)
  - Coster, Trinka, 1990; UA075.002.050.00007 (Box 50)
  - Cotsen, Thomas Adam, 1990; UA075.002.050.00008 (Box 50)
  - Cotsen, Martha, 1990; UA075.002.050.00009 (Box 50)
  - Counelis, George, 1995; UA075.002.050.00010 (Box 50)
  - Coviello, Michele, 1993; UA075.002.050.00011 (Box 50)
  - Covington, Benjamin, 1988; UA075.002.050.00012 (Box 50)
  - Crans, Charles, 1991; UA075.002.050.00013 (Box 50)
  - Crans, Mara (formerly Lambert, Mara), 1992; UA075.002.050.00014 (Box 50)
  - Cremisi, Henry David, 1988; UA075.002.050.00015 (Box 50)
  - Crider, Anja - see Bergman, Anja, 1992; UA075.002.050.00016 (Box 50)
  - Cremone, Jeralyn, 1990; UA075.002.050.00017 (Box 50)
  - Croke, John, 1986; UA075.002.050.00018 (Box 50)
  - Cronin, Claire, 1995; UA075.002.050.00019 (Box 50)
  - Crowley, Kathleen, 1992; UA075.002.050.00020 (Box 50)
  - Cuddihy, Maria (formerly Marin-Padilla, Maria), 1989; UA075.002.050.00021 (Box 50)
  - Culbert, Steven, 1995; UA075.002.050.00022 (Box 50)
  - Cummings, Robert, 1990; UA075.002.050.00023 (Box 50)
  - Cummins, Dean, 1988; UA075.002.050.00024 (Box 50)
  - Cunningham, David, 1987; UA075.002.050.00025 (Box 50)
  - Cunningham, Patrick, 1994; UA075.002.050.00026 (Box 50)
  - Cuozzo, Lilia, 1992; UA075.002.050.00027 (Box 50)
  - Curran, Deidre, 1989; UA075.002.050.00028 (Box 50)
  - Curtin, Francis, 1987; UA075.002.050.00029 (Box 50)
  - Curtis, Brian, 1986; UA075.002.050.00030 (Box 50)
  - Curtis, Sean, 1990; UA075.002.050.00031 (Box 50)
  - Czarniak - see Cremone, 1990; UA075.002.050.00032 (Box 50)
  - Daane, Stephen, 1989; UA075.002.051.00001 (Box 51)
  - D'Agincourt, Paul, 1988; UA075.002.051.00002 (Box 51)
  - Daley, Luke, 1987; UA075.002.051.00003 (Box 51)
  - Dalprymple, Neal, 1992; UA075.002.051.00004 (Box 51)
  - Dambek, Suzanne, 1994; UA075.002.051.00005 (Box 51)
  - D'Ambrosio, Paul, 1988; UA075.002.051.00006 (Box 51)
  - Danehy, Edward, 1988; UA075.002.051.00007 (Box 51)
  - Dang, Anh-Nhi, 1992; UA075.002.051.00008 (Box 51)
  - D'Angelica, Michael, 1993; UA075.002.051.00009 (Box 51)
  - D'Angelo, Carrie, 1995; UA075.002.051.00010 (Box 51)
  - Davidow, Peter, 1986; UA075.002.051.00011 (Box 51)
  - Davidson, Ralph, 1994; UA075.002.051.00012 (Box 51)
  - Davidson, Karen, 1991; UA075.002.051.00013 (Box 51)
  - Day, Mary, 1987; UA075.002.051.00014 (Box 51)
  - DeAngelis, Christopher, 1993; UA075.002.051.00015 (Box 51)
  - DeBroff, Brian, 1989; UA075.002.051.00016 (Box 51)
  - Decker, Douglas, 1990; UA075.002.051.00017 (Box 51)
  - Deckey, George, 1988; UA075.002.051.00018 (Box 51)
  - Deckey, Gowan, 1989; UA075.002.051.00019 (Box 51)
  - Deegan, William, 1988; UA075.002.051.00020 (Box 51)
  - De Ferranti, Sarah, 1991 -- 1995; UA075.002.051.00021 (Box 51)
  - DeFerrante, Diane, 1991 -- 1995; UA075.002.051.00022 (Box 51)
  - DeJong, John, 1985 -- 1987; UA075.002.051.00023 (Box 51)
  - DeJesus, Dennis, 1984 -- 1988; UA075.002.051.00024 (Box 51)
  - Del Valle, Michelle, 1987 -- 1991; UA075.002.051.00025 (Box 51)
  - Demby, Brian, 1982 -- 1986; UA075.002.051.00026 (Box 51)
  - Dempsey, Peter, 1982 -- 1986; UA075.002.051.00027 (Box 51)
  - DeNofrio, David, 1984 -- 1988; UA075.002.051.00028 (Box 51)
  - Derose, Stephen, 1987 -- 1991; UA075.002.051.00029 (Box 51)
  - Desai, Parul, 1988 -- 1992; UA075.002.051.00030 (Box 51)
  - Garcia-Moliner, Maria, 1988; UA075.002.052.00001 (Box 52)
  - Garrell, David, 1987; UA075.002.052.00002 (Box 52)
  - Garrell, Ronald, 1986; UA075.002.052.00003 (Box 52)
  - Garten, Alan, 1986; UA075.002.052.00004 (Box 52)
  - Gastwirt Pamela Cheney, 1994; UA075.002.052.00005 (Box 52)
  - Gatto, Carl, 1994; UA075.002.052.00006 (Box 52)
  - Gatzimos, Alexander Christos, 1986; UA075.002.052.00007 (Box 52)
  - Gatzimos, Kimbery, 1987; UA075.002.052.00008 (Box 52)
  - Gavazz (see Moser), 1991; UA075.002.052.00009 (Box 52)
  - Gaynor, Chrisopher, 1993; UA075.002.052.00010 (Box 52)
  - Gazzara, Lisa Calascibetta, 1992; UA075.002.052.00011 (Box 52)
  - Gealow, Mary Condello, 1993; UA075.002.052.00012 (Box 52)
  - Gee, Beatrice, 1987; UA075.002.052.00013 (Box 52)
  - Gee, Everett, 1986; UA075.002.052.00014 (Box 52)
  - Geltzer, Allen, 1995; UA075.002.052.00015 (Box 52)
  - George, Michael, 1989; UA075.002.052.00016 (Box 52)
  - Gervais, Debra, 1990; UA075.002.052.00017 (Box 52)
  - Getch, Christopher, 1989; UA075.002.052.00018 (Box 52)
  - Gherardi, Peter, 1989; UA075.002.052.00019 (Box 52)
  - Ghorbani, Reza, 1992; UA075.002.052.00020 (Box 52)
  - Gibb, Eric, 1995; UA075.002.052.00021 (Box 52)
  - Gidday, Amy, 1993; UA075.002.052.00022 (Box 52)
  - Gilfeather Ayres, Maryellyn, 1989; UA075.002.052.00023 (Box 52)
  - Gill, Edward, 1986; UA075.002.052.00024 (Box 52)
  - Gilman, Matthew, 1992; UA075.002.052.00025 (Box 52)
  - Giuffrida, Michael, 1989; UA075.002.052.00026 (Box 52)
  - Gladstone, James, 1990; UA075.002.053.00001 (Box 53)
  - Glass, Kathryn, 1995; UA075.002.053.00002 (Box 53)
  - Glassman, Bruce, 1988; UA075.002.053.00003 (Box 53)
  - Glennon, James, 1986; UA075.002.053.00004 (Box 53)
  - Glockman-Simon, Richard, 1986; UA075.002.053.00005 (Box 53)
  - Glynne, Rose, 1988; UA075.002.053.00006 (Box 53)
  - Godin, Celine, 1994; UA075.002.053.00007 (Box 53)
  - Goh, Jodi Paige (see Malis), 1994; UA075.002.053.00008 (Box 53)
  - Goh, Keow Mei, 1993; UA075.002.053.00009 (Box 53)
  - Goh, William, 1992; UA075.002.053.00010 (Box 53)
  - Gokce, Noyan, 1992; UA075.002.053.00011 (Box 53)
  - Gold, Rosalind, 1991; UA075.002.053.00012 (Box 53)
  - Goldberg, Cynthia, 1988; UA075.002.053.00013 (Box 53)
  - Goldberg, David, 1993; UA075.002.053.00014 (Box 53)
  - Goldberg, Jay, 1995; UA075.002.053.00015 (Box 53)
  - Goldenson, Richard, 1992; UA075.002.053.00016 (Box 53)
  - Goldfarb, Adam, 1986; UA075.002.053.00017 (Box 53)
  - Goldfarb, Miriam, 1994; UA075.002.053.00018 (Box 53)
  - Goldstein, Andrew, 1995; UA075.002.053.00019 (Box 53)
  - Goldstein, Rachel, 1990; UA075.002.053.00020 (Box 53)
  - Goldston, James, 1987; UA075.002.053.00021 (Box 53)
  - Goldyn, Lawrence, 1988; UA075.002.053.00022 (Box 53)
  - Gomez, Fernando, 1992; UA075.002.053.00023 (Box 53)
  - Gonsalves, Arthur, 1991; UA075.002.053.00024 (Box 53)
  - Goodarzi, Katayoon, 1993; UA075.002.053.00025 (Box 53)
  - Goodman, Louise, 1992; UA075.002.053.00026 (Box 53)
  - Goodman, William, 1989; UA075.002.053.00027 (Box 53)
  - Goodnight, James, 1988; UA075.002.053.00028 (Box 53)
  - Goodpasture, Dana (see Miller), 1994; UA075.002.053.00029 (Box 53)
  - Goolishian, Wade, 1986; UA075.002.053.00030 (Box 53)
  - Kanhouwa, Meera, 1988; UA075.002.054.00001 (Box 54)
  - Kanter, Sue, 1994; UA075.002.054.00002 (Box 54)
  - Kao, Grace, 1995; UA075.002.054.00003 (Box 54)
  - Kaplan, Jeffrey, 1986; UA075.002.054.00004 (Box 54)
  - Kaplan, Michael, 1992; UA075.002.054.00005 (Box 54)
  - Karageozian, Wicken, 1995; UA075.002.054.00006 (Box 54)
  - Karas, Richard, 1986; UA075.002.054.00007 (Box 54)
  - Kardos, Leslie, 1990; UA075.002.054.00008 (Box 54)
  - Karplus, Theresa, 1992; UA075.002.054.00009 (Box 54)
  - Karshbaum, Stephen, 1991; UA075.002.054.00010 (Box 54)
  - Karwowski, John (Jan), 1995; UA075.002.054.00011 (Box 54)
  - Kastenberg, Judith, 1994; UA075.002.054.00012 (Box 54)
  - Kastrinakis, William, 1990; UA075.002.054.00013 (Box 54)
  - Kates, Andrew, 1994; UA075.002.054.00014 (Box 54)
  - Katz, Josh, 1992; UA075.002.054.00015 (Box 54)
  - Kaufer, David, 1993; UA075.002.054.00016 (Box 54)
  - Kavanagh, Brian, 1993; UA075.002.054.00017 (Box 54)
  - Kearney, Patricia, 1986; UA075.002.054.00018 (Box 54)
  - Keisch, Martin, 1987; UA075.002.054.00019 (Box 54)
  - Kelley, Jean, 1987; UA075.002.054.00020 (Box 54)
  - Kelliher, Elinor, 1995; UA075.002.054.00021 (Box 54)
  - Kellogg, Kim, 1992; UA075.002.054.00022 (Box 54)
  - Kelly, Kathleen A. (see LaRosa), 1995; UA075.002.054.00023 (Box 54)
  - Kenet, Stacia, 1989; UA075.002.054.00024 (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Jeffrey, 1987; UA075.002.054.00025 (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Joseph, 1990; UA075.002.054.00026 (Box 54)
  - Kennedy, Maryellen, 1987; UA075.002.054.00027 (Box 54)
  - Kenny, Rose (see Choquette), 1995; UA075.002.054.00028 (Box 54)
  - Kentopp, Kristin, 1994; UA075.002.054.00029 (Box 54)
  - Keroack, Eric, 1986; UA075.002.055.00001 (Box 55)
  - Keroack, Myles, 1988; UA075.002.055.00002 (Box 55)
  - Kerrigan, David, 1987; UA075.002.055.00003 (Box 55)
  - Kesling, Kimberly, 1990; UA075.002.055.00004 (Box 55)
  - Kessler, Robert, 1992; UA075.002.055.00005 (Box 55)
  - Khaleeli, Hosayn, 1995; UA075.002.055.00006 (Box 55)
  - Khan, Amir, 1994; UA075.002.055.00007 (Box 55)
  - Khouri, Sami, 1995; UA075.002.055.00008 (Box 55)
  - Khoury (Scatamacchia), Sandra, 1986; UA075.002.055.00009 (Box 55)
  - Kiang, Margaret (See Chen), 1995; UA075.002.055.00010 (Box 55)
  - Kiatboonsri, Charn, 1990; UA075.002.055.00011 (Box 55)
  - Kiely, Philip, 1987; UA075.002.055.00012 (Box 55)
  - Kiger, Lydia, 1991; UA075.002.055.00013 (Box 55)
  - Kilian, Raige, 1995; UA075.002.055.00014 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Christopher, 1991; UA075.002.055.00015 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Helen, 1992; UA075.002.055.00016 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Henry, 1990; UA075.002.055.00017 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Jean, 1992; UA075.002.055.00018 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Joanne, 1993; UA075.002.055.00019 (Box 55)
  - Kim, Tae, 1990; UA075.002.055.00020 (Box 55)
  - Kimura, Mitchell, 1993; UA075.002.055.00021 (Box 55)
  - Kindy, Rose (See Glynne), 1988; UA075.002.055.00022 (Box 55)
  - King, Mary, 1986; UA075.002.055.00023 (Box 55)
  - Kittredge, Rebecca (See Rosenstein), 1995; UA075.002.055.00024 (Box 55)
  - Kizilay, Lerzan, 1991; UA075.002.055.00025 (Box 55)
  - Klein, David, 1993; UA075.002.055.00026 (Box 55)
  - Klein, Richard, 1993; UA075.002.055.00027 (Box 55)
  - Kletzky, Deborah, 1988; UA075.002.055.00028 (Box 55)
  - Knowles, John, 1986; UA075.002.055.00029 (Box 55)
  - Ko, Ellen, 1992; UA075.002.055.00030 (Box 55)
  - Ko, Tien-Hoa, 1991; UA075.002.056.00001 (Box 56)
  - Kohn, James, 1989; UA075.002.056.00002 (Box 56)
  - Kolker, Dov, 1994; UA075.002.056.00003 (Box 56)
  - Koobatian, Gregor, 1989; UA075.002.056.00004 (Box 56)
  - Korman, Laura, 1991; UA075.002.056.00005 (Box 56)
  - Kornfield, Elizabeth, 1993; UA075.002.056.00006 (Box 56)
  - Koury, Michelle, 1993; UA075.002.056.00007 (Box 56)
  - Koutsos, Martha, 1986; UA075.002.056.00008 (Box 56)
  - Kramer, Jonathan (Jonah), 1989; UA075.002.056.00009 (Box 56)
  - Kramer, Michelle, 1995; UA075.002.056.00010 (Box 56)
  - Krasner, Stephen, 1986; UA075.002.056.00011 (Box 56)
  - Krata, Lewis, 1988; UA075.002.056.00012 (Box 56)
  - Krosnick, Steven, 1987; UA075.002.056.00013 (Box 56)
  - Krusell, Allan, 1986; UA075.002.056.00014 (Box 56)
  - Kruy, Peter, 1988; UA075.002.056.00015 (Box 56)
  - Krystal, Alan, 1990; UA075.002.056.00016 (Box 56)
  - Kudva, Archana, 1993; UA075.002.056.00017 (Box 56)
  - Kulicki, Leonard, 1990; UA075.002.056.00018 (Box 56)
  - Kulleseid, Sara, 1995; UA075.002.056.00019 (Box 56)
  - Kunins, Lisa, 1995; UA075.002.056.00020 (Box 56)
  - Kutchemeshgi, Mitra, 1994; UA075.002.056.00021 (Box 56)
  - Kwan, Myron, 1989; UA075.002.056.00022 (Box 56)
  - Kwon, Jay, 1990; UA075.002.056.00023 (Box 56)
  - Laband, Paul, 1993; UA075.002.056.00024 (Box 56)
  - Labbate, Lawrence, 1986; UA075.002.056.00025 (Box 56)
  - Lac, Tri, 1993; UA075.002.056.00026 (Box 56)
  - Laitin, Steven, 1991; UA075.002.056.00027 (Box 56)
  - Lake Hooten, Josephine, 1994; UA075.002.056.00028 (Box 56)
  - Lam, Raymond, 1995; UA075.002.056.00029 (Box 56)
  - LaMar, Cindy, 1993; UA075.002.057.00001 (Box 56)
  - Lambert, Kathleen, 1995; UA075.002.057.00002 (Box 57)
  - Lamonica, Gene, 1992; UA075.002.057.00003 (Box 57)
  - Lan, Yueh-Tze, 1991; UA075.002.057.00004 (Box 57)
  - Landrio, Mark, 1993; UA075.002.057.00005 (Box 57)
  - Landrio, Julie, 1995; UA075.002.057.00006 (Box 57)
  - Landry, Daniel, 1988; UA075.002.057.00007 (Box 57)
  - Landry, Francis, 1987; UA075.002.057.00008 (Box 57)
  - Lane, Brian, 1988; UA075.002.057.00009 (Box 57)
  - Lane, Leewood, 1986; UA075.002.057.00010 (Box 57)
  - Langlieb, Alan, 1992; UA075.002.057.00011 (Box 57)
  - Lapidus, Simons, 1997; UA075.002.057.00012 (Box 57)
  - Larcom, Peter, 1989; UA075.002.057.00013 (Box 57)
  - Lareau, Greg, 1986; UA075.002.057.00014 (Box 57)
  - LaRosa, Kathleen Kelly, 1995; UA075.002.057.00015 (Box 57)
  - Larrabee, Joan, 1993; UA075.002.057.00016 (Box 57)
  - Laskin, William, 1991; UA075.002.057.00017 (Box 57)
  - Lattouf, Maria, 1994; UA075.002.057.00018 (Box 57)
  - Lau, Wayne, 1991; UA075.002.057.00019 (Box 57)
  - Lauritzen, Derek, 1992; UA075.002.057.00020 (Box 57)
  - Lauze, Scott, 1990; UA075.002.057.00021 (Box 57)
  - Lavin, William, 1986; UA075.002.057.00022 (Box 57)
  - Law, Amy, 1992; UA075.002.057.00023 (Box 57)
  - Lawson, Kenneth, 1990; UA075.002.057.00024 (Box 57)
  - Lazinger, Maxwell, 1990; UA075.002.057.00025 (Box 57)
  - Le, Kim Chi Thi, 1995; UA075.002.057.00026 (Box 57)
  - Le, Thong Phuoc, 1990; UA075.002.057.00027 (Box 57)
  - Leavitt, Jeffrey, 1986; UA075.002.057.00028 (Box 57)
  - Lederman, Kimberly, 1993; UA075.002.057.00029 (Box 57)
  - Lee, Chinfun, 1995; UA075.002.058.00001 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Christina, 1992; UA075.002.058.00002 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Elton, 1993; UA075.002.058.00003 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Eugene, 1994; UA075.002.058.00004 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Gerald, 1994; UA075.002.058.00005 (Box 58)
  - Lee, John, 1992; UA075.002.058.00006 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Judy, 1995; UA075.002.058.00007 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Karl, 1992; UA075.002.058.00008 (Box 58)
  - Lee, K. Philip, 1990; UA075.002.058.00009 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Loretta, 1995; UA075.002.058.00010 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Michael, 1993; UA075.002.058.00011 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Prescott, 1993; UA075.002.058.00012 (Box 58)
  - Lee, Sara Jane, 1994; UA075.002.058.00013 (Box 58)
  - Lee, The Min, 1992; UA075.002.058.00014 (Box 58)
  - Lee-Parritz, Aviva, 1988; UA075.002.058.00015 (Box 58)
  - Legare, Edward, 1989; UA075.002.058.00016 (Box 58)
  - Legare, Robert, 1990; UA075.002.058.00017 (Box 58)
  - Leisk, Jeanette, 1993; UA075.002.058.00018 (Box 58)
  - Lembo, Anthony, 1990; UA075.002.058.00019 (Box 58)
  - Leng, Wendy, 1991; UA075.002.058.00020 (Box 58)
  - Lentz, Kathleen, 1988; UA075.002.058.00021 (Box 58)
  - Lerner, Richard, 1989; UA075.002.058.00022 (Box 58)
  - Leung, Eleanor, 1991; UA075.002.058.00023 (Box 58)
  - Leung, Yat, 1995; UA075.002.058.00024 (Box 58)
  - Lisser, Amy, 1986; UA075.002.059.00001 (Box 59)
  - Little, Frederic, 1993; UA075.002.059.00002 (Box 59)
  - Liu, David, 1994; UA075.002.059.00003 (Box 59)
  - Llyod, Erika, 1993; UA075.002.059.00004 (Box 59)
  - Loffman-Felman, Rina, 1995; UA075.002.059.00005 (Box 59)
  - London, Diane, 1991; UA075.002.059.00006 (Box 59)
  - Looby-Gordon, Sandra, 1987; UA075.002.059.00007 (Box 59)
  - Lopes, Gary, 1987; UA075.002.059.00008 (Box 59)
  - Lopez, Wilberto, 1989; UA075.002.059.00009 (Box 59)
  - LoPreiato, Matteo, 1988; UA075.002.059.00010 (Box 59)
  - LoPreste, Gail, 1989; UA075.002.059.00011 (Box 59)
  - Lorenze, Mark, 1992; UA075.002.059.00012 (Box 59)
  - Lown, David, 1994; UA075.002.059.00013 (Box 59)
  - Lu, Amy, 1993; UA075.002.059.00014 (Box 59)
  - Lu, Louise, 1986; UA075.002.059.00015 (Box 59)
  - Luftman, Debra, 1987; UA075.002.059.00016 (Box 59)
  - Lum, Daryl, 1995; UA075.002.059.00017 (Box 59)
  - Lum, Kirk, 1993; UA075.002.059.00018 (Box 59)
  - Lumpkin, Monica, 1994; UA075.002.059.00019 (Box 59)
  - Lundy, Carolyn, 1988; UA075.002.059.00020 (Box 59)
  - Lundy, Geoffrey, 1986; UA075.002.059.00021 (Box 59)
  - Luong, Kevin, 1995; UA075.002.059.00022 (Box 59)
  - Ly, Dat, 1995; UA075.002.059.00023 (Box 59)
  - Ly, Thuytien, 1994; UA075.002.059.00024 (Box 59)
  - Lykkeberg, Norman, 1992; UA075.002.059.00025 (Box 59)
  - Lynch, Michael, 1989; UA075.002.059.00026 (Box 59)
  - Levenson, Aryeh, 1990; UA075.002.060.00001 (Box 60)
  - Levenstein, Laura, 1993; UA075.002.060.00002 (Box 60)
  - Leventhal, Todd, 1992; UA075.002.060.00003 (Box 60)
  - Levey, Douglas, 1990; UA075.002.060.00004 (Box 60)
  - Levin, Richard, 1987; UA075.002.060.00005 (Box 60)
  - Levin, Scott, 1993; UA075.002.060.00006 (Box 60)
  - Levine, Eric, 1990; UA075.002.060.00007 (Box 60)
  - Levitsky, Kenneth, 1986; UA075.002.060.00008 (Box 60)
  - Levy, Allen, 1991; UA075.002.060.00009 (Box 60)
  - Levy, Kenneth, 1986; UA075.002.060.00010 (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Carol, 1988; UA075.002.060.00011 (Box 60)
  - Lewis, Susan, 1992; UA075.002.060.00012 (Box 60)
  - Lewis Burns, Sophia, 1989; UA075.002.060.00013 (Box 60)
  - Li, Sharon, 1994; UA075.002.060.00014 (Box 60)
  - Licht, Ann, 1995; UA075.002.060.00015 (Box 60)
  - Lieberman, Douglas, 1994; UA075.002.060.00016 (Box 60)
  - Liederman, Eric, 1989; UA075.002.060.00017 (Box 60)
  - Liedtka, Jane, 1986; UA075.002.060.00018 (Box 60)
  - Limentani, Steven, 1986; UA075.002.060.00019 (Box 60)
  - Lin, Helen, 1994; UA075.002.060.00020 (Box 60)
  - Lin, Ian, 1994; UA075.002.060.00021 (Box 60)
  - Lin, Roy, 1995; UA075.002.060.00022 (Box 60)
  - Lin, Shan, 1994; UA075.002.060.00023 (Box 60)
  - Link, Mark, 1986; UA075.002.060.00024 (Box 60)
  - Linker, Seth, 1993; UA075.002.060.00025 (Box 60)
  - Lippincott, Tyler, 1986; UA075.002.060.00026 (Box 60)
  - Lipsky, Mark, 1987; UA075.002.060.00027 (Box 60)
  - Lyons, Daniel, 1987; UA075.002.061.00001 (Box 61)
  - Lystad, Lisa, 1987; UA075.002.061.00002 (Box 61)
  - MacDonnell, Sheila, 1995; UA075.002.061.00003 (Box 61)
  - Macek, James, 1986; UA075.002.061.00004 (Box 61)
  - MacGillivray, John, 1990; UA075.002.061.00005 (Box 61)
  - MacGillivray, Thomas, 1988; UA075.002.061.00006 (Box 61)
  - Mack, Charles, 1992; UA075.002.061.00007 (Box 61)
  - MacKoul, David, 1987; UA075.002.061.00008 (Box 61)
  - MacKoul, Paul, 1989; UA075.002.061.00009 (Box 61)
  - MacMillan, Christine, 1995; UA075.002.061.00010 (Box 61)
  - Macoul, Katherine, 1991; UA075.002.061.00011 (Box 61)
  - Madaras, Laszlo, 1993; UA075.002.061.00012 (Box 61)
  - Maggio, Louis, 1992; UA075.002.061.00013 (Box 61)
  - Maghsoudy, Afsaneh, 1994; UA075.002.061.00014 (Box 61)
  - Magnante, David, 1989; UA075.002.061.00015 (Box 61)
  - Maguire, Richard, 1991; UA075.002.061.00016 (Box 61)
  - Maheras, Stylianos, 1995; UA075.002.061.00017 (Box 61)
  - Mahoney, Kathleen, 1986; UA075.002.061.00018 (Box 61)
  - Mahoney, Sharon, 1987; UA075.002.061.00019 (Box 61)
  - Mainiero, Martha, 1989; UA075.002.061.00020 (Box 61)
  - Maiorano, Philip, 1987; UA075.002.061.00021 (Box 61)
  - Major, Nancy, 1988; UA075.002.061.00022 (Box 61)
  - Malaquias, Lisa, 1991; UA075.002.061.00023 (Box 61)
  - Malcynski, John, 1991; UA075.002.061.00024 (Box 61)
  - Malis, Jodi, 1994; UA075.002.061.00025 (Box 61)
  - Mallen, John, 1988; UA075.002.061.00026 (Box 61)
  - Malley, Richard, 1990; UA075.002.061.00027 (Box 61)
  - Malone, Debra, 1993; UA075.002.061.00028 (Box 61)
  - Maloney, Alan, 1990; UA075.002.062.00001 (Box 62)
  - Mambrino, Larry, 1986; UA075.002.062.00002 (Box 62)
  - Manayan, Rex, 1991; UA075.002.062.00003 (Box 62)
  - Mang, Dzung, 1994; UA075.002.062.00004 (Box 62)
  - Manickas, Alexa, 1989; UA075.002.062.00005 (Box 62)
  - Mann, Karen, 1988; UA075.002.062.00006 (Box 62)
  - Mann, Nancy, 1991; UA075.002.062.00007 (Box 62)
  - Manolidis, Spiros, 1988; UA075.002.062.00008 (Box 62)
  - Manoukian, Paul, 1989; UA075.002.062.00009 (Box 62)
  - Manseau, Christopher, 1991; UA075.002.062.00010 (Box 62)
  - Mansour, Marc, 1990; UA075.002.062.00011 (Box 62)
  - Manzano, Ramiro, 1990; UA075.002.062.00012 (Box 62)
  - Marble, Kim, 1989; UA075.002.062.00013 (Box 62)
  - Marin-Padilla, Maria, 1989; UA075.002.062.00014 (Box 62)
  - Marks, Jeffrey, 1987; UA075.002.062.00015 (Box 62)
  - Maroko, Deborah, 1995; UA075.002.062.00016 (Box 62)
  - Maroko, Robert, 1995; UA075.002.062.00017 (Box 62)
  - Marshall, John, 1986; UA075.002.062.00018 (Box 62)
  - Marshall, Sharon, 1993; UA075.002.062.00019 (Box 62)
  - Martin, Bernadette, 1988; UA075.002.062.00020 (Box 62)
  - Martinez, Lance, 1995; UA075.002.062.00021 (Box 62)
  - Martinucci, Michael, 1991; UA075.002.062.00022 (Box 62)
  - Marzette, Debbie, 1989; UA075.002.062.00023 (Box 62)
  - Mascola, Maria, 1989; UA075.002.062.00024 (Box 62)
  - Massa, Robert, 1989; UA075.002.062.00025 (Box 62)
  - Mathews, Katherine, 1992; UA075.002.062.00026 (Box 62)
  - Matook, George, 1988; UA075.002.063.00001 (Box 63)
  - May, Sarah, 1991; UA075.002.063.00002 (Box 63)
  - May, Mary Patricia, 1986; UA075.002.063.00003 (Box 63)
  - Maynard, Karen, 1994; UA075.002.063.00004 (Box 63)
  - Mazur, Holly, 1992; UA075.002.063.00005 (Box 63)
  - McAfee, Steven, 1987; UA075.002.063.00006 (Box 63)
  - McAteer, Allison, 1995; UA075.002.063.00007 (Box 63)
  - McConville, Owen, 1986; UA075.002.063.00008 (Box 63)
  - McCormick, Danny, 1991; UA075.002.063.00009 (Box 63)
  - McCullen, Jennifer, 1990; UA075.002.063.00010 (Box 63)
  - McDonald, David, 1991; UA075.002.063.00011 (Box 63)
  - McDonald, Jennifer, 1993; UA075.002.063.00012 (Box 63)
  - McDonald, Scott, 1988; UA075.002.063.00013 (Box 63)
  - McGaugh, Mary, 1988; UA075.002.063.00014 (Box 63)
  - McGoldrick, John, 1987; UA075.002.063.00015 (Box 63)
  - McGonigle, Laurie, 1994; UA075.002.063.00016 (Box 63)
  - McGowan, Katherine, 1994; UA075.002.063.00017 (Box 63)
  - McInerny, Jane, 1990; UA075.002.063.00018 (Box 63)
  - McKnight, Timothy, 1987; UA075.002.063.00019 (Box 63)
  - McMichael, Pamela, 1993; UA075.002.063.00020 (Box 63)
  - Meany, Madalon, 1987; UA075.002.063.00021 (Box 63)
  - Meckler, Ken, 1994; UA075.002.063.00022 (Box 63)
  - Mehlman, George, 1989; UA075.002.063.00023 (Box 63)
  - Mehta, Tejas, 1992; UA075.002.063.00024 (Box 63)
  - Melanson, Gerard, 1987; UA075.002.063.00025 (Box 63)
  - Meline, Daniel, 1987; UA075.002.063.00026 (Box 63)
  - Meltzer, Bruce, 1987; UA075.002.063.00027 (Box 63)
  - Mester-Fitzgerald, Maria, 1986; UA075.002.063.00028 (Box 63)
  - Metzger, Amanda, 1993; UA075.002.063.00029 (Box 63)
  - Metzger, Jonathan, 1993; UA075.002.064.00001 (Box 64)
  - Michaud, Marc, 1993; UA075.002.064.00002 (Box 64)
  - Miller, Andrew, 1995; UA075.002.064.00003 (Box 64)
  - Miller, Dana, 1994; UA075.002.064.00004 (Box 64)
  - Miller, Eric, 1990; UA075.002.064.00005 (Box 64)
  - Mitchell, Robert, 1990; UA075.002.064.00006 (Box 64)
  - Mitchell, Judith, 1987; UA075.002.064.00007 (Box 64)
  - Mitchell, William, 1994; UA075.002.064.00008 (Box 64)
  - Mitri, Carol, 1987; UA075.002.064.00009 (Box 64)
  - Moasser, Mehrdad, 1988; UA075.002.064.00010 (Box 64)